Hi guys!
I'm going to make a vegetarian version of the enchiladas for the vegetarian of the house.
I got my beef, chicken, now I'm doing the vegetable enchilada.
What I want to do is I want to get this yellow bell pepper.
You can use green or you can use red.
I just like the color of yellow and I'm going to use yellow.
What you want to do is you want to cut half down the middle.
I'm going to use this for later on.
Basically, just slice big thick slices kind of like you would a chicken.
This inner part of the bell pepper you want to take out of there because that's no good.
Put that aside and any of the stick white that you see here kind of take that out.
You just want the flesh.
You definitely want to wash your bell pepper before.
I've already done that.
What I'm going to do is I'm going to slice this just like you would chicken strips for fajita.
Put that aside.
Now same thing with the onion.
I'm going to use half an onion.
You want to use the same amount of onion as you would the bell pepper.
Make sure to get all that stuff peeled off that I was talking about, all that nastiness.
You just want to cut this down into long slices.
Just like that.
As far as preparing for this, you want to lightly coat this with some extra virgin olive oil.
That way the seasoning is going to stick.
Stick some fresh ground black pepper.
You want to evenly coat all the vegetables.
You're definitely going to need some salt.
As far as salt and pepper goes, you just want to eyeball it and season to taste.
Me, I'm just going to season that's probably about 1-2 teaspoons.
Then I'm also going to use a little garlic powder.
What you want to do is you want to toss all that together.
If you want to add any other type of seasoning, paprika, cayenne pepper, anything you can.
It's up to you.
This is just my simple enchilada recipe and this is the vegetarian version.
As far as the vegetarian enchiladas, I'm also going to have spinach, but these already nicely washed and ready to go and I'm also going to adds some cheese to all the enchiladas.
This is not what all that's going to go into your enchilada.
As far as preparing for it, you want to go and preheat your pan again.
I already washed it and everything.
The same pan that we cooked the chicken and beef, I washed it and I preheated it and it's nice and hot.
You don't even have to add oil because you stuck the oil on the onion and bell pepper earlier.
And that is how you prepare your vegetables for you vegetarian enchilada.